<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright (c) 2017 Reto Inderbitzin (mail@indr.ch)
  ~
  ~ For the full copyright and license information, please view
  ~ the LICENSE file that was distributed with this source code.
  -->

<resources>

    <string name="speech_welcome_short">Welcome to three three five.</string>
    <string name="speech_welcome_long">Welcome to three three five. Easy navigation to thousands of online radio stations, as well as media on your device.</string>

    <string name="speech_ui_selection">Select interface: Press on the right half to launch the button interface, left half to launch the list interface.</string>

    <string name="speech_interface_instructions"><![CDATA[
Welcome to the three three five button interface navigation screen.\n\
\n\
You can long press anywhere ON THIS SCREEN to hear the button description.\n\
PLEASE LISTEN FOR BUTTON DESCRIPTIONs.\n\
This screen has 3 rows of buttons.\n\
\n\
The top  TWO rowS HAVE 3 navigation buttons.\n\
the 3rd row has 5.\n\
THREE THREE  FIVE \n\
\n\
Starting from left to right.\n\
ROW NUMBER 1.\n\
FIRST.\n\
Top Left IS HOME button.\n\
Pressing HOME all ways brings you back to the top of your chosen category.\n\
Second:\n\
Top Center is Back button.\n\
Pressing BACK  takes you one step back.\n\
Third:\n\
Top right is location button.\n\
Pressing LOCATION will tell you where you are in the file and folder structure.\n\
ROW NUMBER 2\n\
First BUTTON IS\n\
PREVIOUS.\n\
PREVIOUS BUTTON Takes you to the last location.\n\
Second BUTTON IS\n\
ENTER.\n\
THIS CENTER button on your screen is like an ENTER button.\n\
This button Enters you into your folder selection or if it\'s a media file or stream, it will load TO PLAY.\n\
Third IS THE NEXT button.\n\
takes you to next folder or next file within CURRENT folder.\n\
\n\
The third bottom row has 5 media player controls for use with media on your device.\n\
First IS Skip.\n\
SKIPS to previous track or file.\n\
Second BUTTON IS seek.\n\
SEEKS 10 seconds back.\n\
Third BUTTON IS: Play AND Pause.\n\
Fourth BUTTON  seekS 10 seconds forward.\n\
Fifth AND FINAL BUTTON  IS SKIP.\n\
SkipS. forward to next track.\n\
\n\
All media files are organized in hierarchical folder structure.\n\
Please feel free to click around to familiarize yourself with three three five navigation,\n\
remember,\n\
you can always click on top right to hear your present location.\n\
\n\
YOU CAN HEAR THESE INSTRUCTIONS AGAIN ANYTIME IN THE PREFERENCES SECTION.\n\
\n\
]]></string>

    <string name="speech_interface_instructions_end_with_home_screen"><![CDATA[
You are now on the home screen on "Music on Your Device".\n\
\n\
Thank you and enjoy three three five.
]]></string>

    <string name="speech_interface_instructions_end_with_preference_screen"><![CDATA[
You are now on the preference screen on "Replay Interface Instructions".\n\
\n\
Thank you and enjoy three three five.
]]></string>

</resources>
